Yeah.
OK, now.
Thanks for recording.
Okay, all right,
so we did the inventory here.
Let's go to the spreadsheet here.
Templates.
Okay, so here we have category.
The family the device belongs to, EEG,
audio interpretation.
Also accepted as category,
category under name, category what was...
But what does this mean?
So in case that you already have the
names in your columns that you need to
modify, is that match with those options?
Okay.
All right, next group, this group name,
the group name,
every unit of its model shares, AE.
Hey, I think you need to rephrase this.
What does this actually mean, group?
That is the device name, right?
Isn't that what it is?
A group.
Yes, but uh,
it's also we take like a group,
so because you have many devices with the
same name.
I understand. Yes, yes, yes. But you know,
when I say group,
I can think about group of the devices,
which is kind of maybe interpretation
receivers is a group of devices.
So it's open up for confusion.
So I think it is better to call this
device name.
or item name.
Okay, yeah, we can just rename that.
Just call it the item name because you
can have many items and then they become
a group of items.
The word group is confusing.
So let's just call it for what it is,
item name.
Okay.
And the only reason why I understood that
was because it says also accept as device
name, device name, item group, etc.
So you don't need to have that also
accepted as. It just confuses people.
Okay, yeah,
we can just add like a last name,
Just, just say this is the item name,
name of the item, yeah.
the item, okay.
Or here you can say, in this field,
the name of the device or item.
That's all you need to say.
Okay.
Serial number unique per unit,
one row per physical device.
Yeah.
Cost, replacements cost as a number.
Brand, yep.
Description left blank.
Yeah, okay.
Ownership.
Okay, taxable location.
No,
you would say here where the device is
located for tax purposes.
Okay.
And leave out talking about jurisdiction,
Miami, Florida, etc.
Just leave it like that.
Okay.
Location.
where the unit physically sits. Yep.
And I don't know why is it that we're
communicating this also accepted as?
Do we need to communicate that?
I said, like...
What's the purpose of communicating that?
Because we don't know how.
how they name that columns in their
original spreadsheet.
It's less worthy if they have to rename
all the columns.
from the arena spreadsheet. So okay,
you already have location or we said that
name with location.
Yeah.
because that's how many options that we
accepted and the system is going to just
map to see, okay,
if your column is named like this one,
I accept it like this.
So you don't need to change it.
Yeah.
All right, well, um...
But why would we do people really need
that?
Because you're also going to have
somebody who comes in and say,
but I want to call it this and then
that's not accepted.
Or do they, why do we have to say that?
I mean,
No, but...
just accept the columns for what they are.
This is the way you have to put it in.
And the only thing we need to do is to
describe what the column is and then tell
them do not change the column names.
Okay, yeah, we can do it mandatory.
I just...
Because we do not want them to change the
column names,
because if they change the column names,
let's say they misspell something,
something get misspelled and then the
system doesn't recognize it. No,
they need to stick to what they are,
you know, having here, you know.
Okay, yeah, we are more strict with that.
No, that's fine.
Exactly.
Do not change the column names and delete
for every single column here,
also accept it, all that, take it away.
OK, yeah, it has to be as it is, OK.
Just delete it, yeah.
Sub locations, comma, set a path.
Okay.
Okay, yeah,
so just a comma separated path inside the
location, outermost first.
So there you can say, I don't know,
like the first location, you can say,
for example, warehouse.
warehouse, Florida warehouse, and then...
What is it called? Karma.
Area 52, room 6, you know.
Okay.
Well, do you want we add the location?
So let's say like we add the pattern for
the example, so say like Miami, Florida.
But that is the pattern,
what I just said here.
A comma separated inside the location out
most first or...
A comma separated path inside the
location.
Delete the outmost first because outmost,
what does that mean? Outmost out,
you know, far the farthest away.
That's kind of like what that can be
All right.
Yeah.
interpreted as. So this delete that.
And then say, for example, is this,
so we have the location.
And you can just say warehouse 2 and then
colon room 65 and then comma shelf 42,
you know.
Okay, yeah, it's uh...
Just put that so people kind of
understand the point that is the path.
And then no defaults. Well, default empty.
You know,
you don't have to say default empty and
delete also accepted as.
The ones that cannot be left empty are
the one that you have the asterisk next
by. Everybody understands that.
Okay.
And that is something, let's see,
this gives you guys your through expected
structure of your Excel file.
Red headers are the only mandatory ones.
Perfect.
You have that communicator already.
So we don't need to say the default empty
here. It's like, this is, you know,
you can fill it out or not.
Gotcha, perfect. Yeah, I'll do it.
I'll do it that way.
Okay.
All right, same here, extra identifiers,
extra identifiers for this unit as key
equals value pair separated by semicolons.
Yeah.
Okay, I think this is good.
So extra identifiers for each unit, colon,
and then key equals value pair separated
by semicolons. For example,
materials equals silicon or Mac equals
this. You know, I think that that's good.
And then...
A value without an equal sign is this is
not accepted.
Okay.
And then delete the default empty and all
that as well.
Yeah.
OK,
and then recommended public URL or image
public URL to picture.
So here is,
we should not do any public URLs that
they can put in here.
We don't want to have the system query
outside of Devitrak.
Okay.
So you have to have an image or it's not
accepted.
And there should be only three image
available, JPEGs, GIFs, or PNGs.
Okay.
All others should not be accepted.
Absolutely no links to anything outside
of Devitrak within Devitrak.
That goes everywhere.
Be careful with that because, you know,
a hacker,
this is a great way of exploiting it.
You know, I'll put a thing in here,
you know,
a dormant link to a Russian server.
that runs some type of commands and or
whatever, you know, you don't want that.
Yeah. No, in case of that,
we can just remove that column and if
they want to add image,
they have to just go through the other
process. So from the add inventory button.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, yes.
And then you can say that in the
Okay, yeah, I did that one.
description. If you need an image,
that would have to be added in the system
separately.
Which sucks because you want to be able
Okay.
to do it. Actually, you know what?
The whole purpose of having a spreadsheet
is that you can add...
many items, you know. So, yeah,
so you should still have the image here,
Right, yeah, that's it.
but you should mandate it's only those
formats.
Okay.
or figure it out,
but it has to be provided at the time of
import.
Yeah.
and limited to those images.
Yeah, I think, no,
I think it's I think it's better just
remove that in that that column and force
them to, if they want it,
they have to go inside the system,
but don't don't have that.
Yes,
but if you have 1000 devices in a
spreadsheet, you want to import a lot,
are you going to sit there and put in
thousand of the same images then? No.
You have to come up with a workaround.
Okay.
They have to be filed,
and we just turn to the 64 base,
and then we just add it to our system.
But we don't accept the public URL.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right, sounds good.
Download the template, take a look at it.
Okay. Whoa.
Yeah,
that's examples just to show how we'll...
Gore.
Yeah.
No, that's good.
Okay, have you tested this yourself?
Yeah, yes.
Okay. All right.
I would encourage you to work on that,
particularly on the image column here,
and then we can look at that further.
You should try it yourself to import.
If you use that on ABC interpreting,
put like 10 units or something, sort in,
and try the images and all that,
and then come back and then we can review
it.
OK, yeah, I'll do it. I'm putting my task.
All right, more options. Update inventory.
Find items, laptops, Chromebooks.
Italian Warehouse.
Continue, I like this.
Continue with 12 items.
Update the group, we're gonna,
they are a little more expensive,
so we're gonna do 300 bucks from flat.
So here, so I'm just going to update this.
If I were to kind of put this in right
now,
what would happen to the location here?
If I don't put stuff in here.
Del.
No,
they're gonna force you to put a location.
Oh.
Yeah, but could you please, if we do that,
since I'm going into an existing group
here,
because I wanted to continue this 12
items,
if I do continue those 12 items and it
said here, ouch, okay, sorry,
more options, update inventory.
So I'm going back here in here, laptops,
we're doing the Chromebooks.
So here 12 items. This is all good.
Why the ownership type? You know,
it's one location since it is one
location and I continue with those items
and I want to work with a whole group and
I only wanted to update the replacement
cost. I don't see why. Why is it that?
You know,
we can't have this pre-populated.
Okay, yeah. So in case that we have more,
well, in this case,
we have only one location that we can
definitely we can just pre-fill the
Correct.
section. We will have more than one.
Sometimes we have multiple locations.
Then you have to leave it, you know.
OK, OK,
so we will leave it like we have right
now,
so that they have to just select the
location.
Okay.
Because like here you have the images
still perfect, the images doesn't change.
I'm happy with that. No,
it's not a container.
Is this device assignable to staff? Yes.
And I remember it is in the IT closet.
This is where it should be. You know,
this is all good,
but if all of them have the same...
location and pre-populate.
Okay.
And you can also say here location.
where the units live and where they are
taxed. They don't live,
but where the units are located.
Okay.
where the units are located.
That's the only thing you can say.
Where units are located, period.
Okay.
And,
and also say that this will be updated
for all,
this will be updated for all the items
upon upon.
I don't know.
Yeah, but we say in the previous step,
so if you want to update the entire group
Okay.
or only one items of the group.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
Okay, so I'll continue to review changes.
All right, 12 items will...
Be updated, you should say.
Will be will be updated.
Okay.
One field that change.
So this is different. This is,
you have to, Gustavo,
I know the English is not your first
language,
but you have to run every piece through
Claudia because you cannot just say this.
Yeah, that's what I no,
but that's what I'm doing.
Yeah.
Okay, good. This one field, that change.
So...
So here, so this particular box here,
like this white box here that is,
you know, you know,
it says the one field that will change
and 10 hour field that keeps today's
value.
I think it's really good what you're
having here.
But you should say these are the changes
that will be made.
Okay.
Hello.
And then you present that here.
What is it that is being changed?
Just like you have it.
But just say to that,
these are the fields that will be changed.
Okay.
Okay, so then it says the whole group,
every item in this group,
whatever its serial number.
There.
There were 12 when you started this
wizard. If one was added since.
It is included, too.
Oh,
so if what you're saying here is every
item is this group.
Will be changed,
and let's say that somebody else added
another Chromebook that that matches the
search criteria that will also be changed.
Is that what you're saying?
Okay, yep.
So let's, no, no, no. So if you have,
let's say you have a really large
operation, you have 50 warehouse managers.
And there is an accountant here who,
because of all the 2000 Chromebooks that
are sitting in different warehouses,
they want to update, you know,
the cost per unit of those because it has
gone up.
But in the meantime,
let's say a few Veriz managers have added
a few Chromebooks since they started this
update process.
What you're saying is that those
Chromebooks that they have added after
the fact that we started this process of
the 12 items here will also be changed.
Is that correct?
It is right, yeah.
Okay, so every item,
even if it is more than 12,
let's say that warehouse manager Gustavo
Rodriguez added another 1000 Chromebooks
that matches the search criteria that we
had here when we started the 12
Chromebooks. They will also be changed.
So the 1000,
now 1012 Chromebooks will be changed.
the cost per unit. Is that correct?
Is that correct?
Okay, all right. Okay, that's good.
So then say, instead of the whole group,
you say, if any other items were added,
That that matches the search that matches
the criteria for this update was added.
They will also be updated,
something like that.
But I know after,
so if they add it after these changes.
Yeah, no,
after then they will not be added.
They shall be.
Outside, OK, OK, just to clear that.
But you know,
when you can say when you click apply to,
just actually don't say apply to 12 items
because that may not be true.
If somebody added more items,
then there will be more items. So.
You know,
you will just say apply at the bottom.
OK.
Because we cannot confirm it is 12 items,
because it could be more or less.
So, but you will say that.
you know,
if items were added during this process
and those items matches the initial
search criteria,
all those items will also be updated.
per this request.
OK, yeah, I wanna add that, remove the 12,
the number, actually,
when I remove person,
gonna just leave the apply label.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But then it's kind of like,
but it's nice to have 12 items will
change at the top.
We may change that later on,
but keep that for now.
I think it's kind of nice because we
assume that it's going to be kind of
smaller businesses that will be used or
smaller groups will be using this in the
beginning.
Okay.
Okay, cool. And I love this. I love this.
I understand this.
Mhm.
I understand this changes one field.
for 12 items.
There is no bulk undo.
Reverting means running this update again.
with the old values. No,
if changes need to be made and there is
no bulk undo.
If additional changes are needed.
Please run another update.
Okay.
Yeah, that's better.
Okay, applies to Charles's 12 changes.
I think it's good that we're recording
this because I don't remember what I'm
saying. All right. Okay.
I think that's it for now.
Do these updates and then we'll do
another run. When can we do that?
Like Tuesday, Wednesday next week,
you think?
Yeah, yeah, I think.
This is not too much, you know,
and I'd rather keep going like more, more,
more, more now,
because I learn from it too, and I can,
I can, you know,
it helps me being able to present the
system.
Yeah, that's that's good,
and that's the idea.
L.
Yeah, I understand the process fully.
All right.
Alright.
So let's call it a day for now,
so I have to eat something also.
Excellent, so let me just stop recording.